I learned to love all kinds of different
music in that group but I always pay
attention of the rhythm that's what I
always like sort of keying on first like
some people will pay attention to melody
or lyrics and for me it's always rhythm
first that's why I love that music with
like real heavier rhythm mean like it's
just like my James you know it gets me
pumped up yeah absolutely
I love it there's so much about that
music that I love like people give me a
hard time they're like how do you listen
to it it's so repetitive every song
sounds like every other song oh my gyno
that's kind of why I like it I only need
one dance move for every song right
we're talking on entire genre of music
one move you're pretty much set you got
to a club or a party just like next song
next song next song right you can't do
that with every different kind of music
like I love rap music and hip hop but
every rap song is trying to have its own
dance move to go with like each song
it's so hard to keep up they want to
teach you how to dougie you got a
Superman you got a stanky leg they want
you to whip and nae nae and dab and juju
on the beat it's like slow down
there's yeah there's a learning curve
here and you're going way too fast
but that means right it's fun right it's
inclusive anybody can dance to it
anybody right Nana you got one good hip
still in the game still in the game get
out there have fun you got no reason not
to dance no excuse I don't have good
rhythm really you don't even need good
rhythm there's literally so much rhythm
in that music it's physically impossible
to be offer them right you miss a beat
there's another beat right behind that
beat just get on the next one it is
repetitive there is a formula right
here's the formula every song st.
beaches then they just put a different
melody over the top of that beat it
doesn't even matter what the melody is
honestly the more repetitive the better
the most famous like techno club song in
the world is three notes three notes the
entire song start-to-finish platinum
three notes just
[Laughter]
you've heard it I know you have exactly
then they do this thing with the vowels
if you never paid attention you can hear
all the vowel sounds in the baseline
right is it true Oh eat eat eat eat Ivan
Ivan Ivan 200 and sometimes why
[Applause]
not always but sometimes why that's not
even the best part the best parts to
break down like three quarters the way
through the song they will drop out the
beat they go with just the melody for
like a little bit build up some suspense
then they bring the beat back real slow
sequentially they build it up and then
it all comes back together in this
moment they call the drop and when that
drop hits people lose their minds yeah I
love it you love it is I feel like it's
the greatest moment in music yeah I
think it's the single greatest moment in
music I feel like I put a head-to-head
with anything like a cymbal crash at the
end of a Beethoven symphony it's got
drama right and suspense there but they
they don't end a lot of songs these days
with a cymbal crash you should notice
that sort of a dying art you don't mean
like it's you know you're not on the
radio like Jasper Seto I don't know why
it's fun they should anyways yeah but
even that moment like that moment that
that slow build and then like I feel
like right when that drop it's I feel
like everything's perfect just for a
second right just just for a moment rats
like I write that first beat gets
everyone's attention it's like
[Music]
[Applause]
I just feel like life's about moments
and just for like that moment that one
moment first second everything's perfect
right boom it's just like sunshine and
rainbows you know buddy just right just
palm puppies ranches home everyone steps
to the back from baggage claim just
[Applause]
[Music]
people get so excited my buddy comes
over a couple weeks ago he's like dude
you got to get the drop on this track he
starts this song up right it's like wait
for it which yeah they always tell you
to wait for he's all excited right this
is the same guy by the way who will
watch a movie with you but he's already
seen the movie and then yeah he's so
excited for you to see it through the
entire movie he's doing this oh watch
this next part
yeah nice I was kind of planning on
watching all of the parts
but just for you on this next section
and I will watch so hard for you
[Music]
he's he's like wait for it wait
wait for it I think I got some stuff to
do today man how long do you think this
like nine minutes later it's like
[Music]
[Applause]
totally worth it I'm so glad I waited
subscribe to drive our comedy for even
more of the world's largest collection
of clean comedy